iwi.com 2011-12-31

# iwi: Privacy Policy

  1. **GENERAL**
    1. Gamesys Limited (“we” or “us”), of 10 Piccadilly, London W1J ODD is a data controller registered with the UK Information Commissioner. We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our terms of service) sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or you provide to us, will be processed by us. By using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. The policy may be amended from time to time. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy. 
    2. Since the Service is only served through social network websites, it is your responsibility to read and accept their terms and conditions, as well as their privacy policy prior to continuing.
  2. **PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED**
    1. When you use the Service, we may record information regarding the use of the Service and, if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may collect other information that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with that website, in particular, your first name, unique user ID, a URL to your social network profile picture and, if you agree, your email address.
  3. **USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**
    1. Your personal information may be collected by us for the following purposes: 
      1. for the purpose of providing the Service. For example, we will use your social network profile picture and your first name to show that you are participating in a game
      2. to enable other users of the Service to access your social network user profile (depending on the privacy and access options chosen by you on your social networking site);
      3. to ensure that content from our Service is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
      4. to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service (Communication Services), when you choose to do so;
      5. to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
    2. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us above, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
    3. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
    4. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. You agree that you will only provide information to us that is accurate, complete and up-to-date and you will notify us of any changes to your personal information.
  4. **DICLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**
    1. We will not sell or give your personally identifiable information to others except as provided in this privacy policy.
    2. We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006 (the “Gamesys Group”).
    3. We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 
      1. in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
      2. if Gamesys Limited, any of its Services, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its users or customers may be one of the assets transferred to that third party. In such circumstances we may retain the right to continue to provide marketing communications relating to other Services provided by us to you;
      3. if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms [http://www.iwi.com/terms.html ] and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Gamesys Limited, members of the Gamesys Group, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
    4. As the Service operates within social networking websites, the Service may share information about you with others in the same social networking site who are using the Service as may be necessary to operate the Service.
    5. By continuing to use the Service, you expressly consent to this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, your consent to use and disclose your personally information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to your information being used in this way, you should not otherwise use the Service. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms.
  5. **STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**
    1. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
  6. **SERVICE SECURITY**
    1. We shall take measures to protect personal information using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, improper use or modification.
    2. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we fully intend to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Service. By accessing and using the Service, you do so at your sole risk and you are responsible for restricting access to your computer and ensuring that your computer is free from all types of malicious code, spyware, viruses, Trojans, etc. that may track any data you enter via this Service, including e-mail address, and payment related information. We are not responsible for any loss or damage arising from the user’s failure to comply with this section.
    3. We reserve the right to monitor all network traffic to this Service to identify and/or block unauthorised attempts or intrusions to upload or change information or cause damage to this Service in any fashion. Anyone using this Service expressly consents to such monitoring.
  7. **COOKIES**
    1. We may store information about you using cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you use our Service in the future. We do this to learn about repeat visitors and to find out if we are delivering quality products and services therefore improving our Service further. During your use of the Services, third party advertisers or other service providers may also place cookies on your computer, over which we have no control. Please check their privacy policies for details of how they use the data they collect in this way.
    2. If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.  
Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org . Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Service.
  8. **CONTACT**
    1. Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to privacy@iwi.com. iwi is a division of Gamesys Limited.
